createnspread.appspot.com 2014-10-17

# Create and Spread Facebook Applications!

Createandspread.com. ("Createandspread.com") knows that you care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. By visiting the [www.Createandspread.com](http://www.createandspred.com/) website and domain name, or otherwise accessing any other linked pages, features, content, or services offered from time to time by in connection therewith (collectively, the "Website"), you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy. 

What Does This Privacy Policy Cover?

This Privacy Policy covers treatment of personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") that gathers when you access the Website and when you use services. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that does not own or control, or to individuals that does not employ or manage.

What Personal Information Does Collect?

The information we gather from customers enables us to personalize and improve our services. We collect the following types of information from our customers:

**Personal Information You Provide to Us:**

We may receive and store any information you enter on our website or provide to us in any other way. The types of Personal Information collected include your full name, email address, IP address, browser information, username, password and any other information necessary for us to provide our services. You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but then you may not be able to take advantage of many of our special features. The Personal Information you provide may be used for such purposes as responding to your requests for certain services, customizing the content you see, and communicating with you about new services.    

**Personal Information Collected Automatically:**

    * We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with our Website or use our services. automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, cookie information, and the page you requested. 
    * Generally, our service automatically collects usage information, such as the numbers and frequency of visitors to our Website and its components, similar to TV ratings that indicate how many people watched a particular show. Createandspread.com only uses this data in aggregate form, that is, as a statistical measure, and not in a manner that would identify you personally. This type of aggregate data enables us to figure out how often customers use parts of the Website or services so that we can make the Website appealing to as many customers as possible, and improve those services. As part of this use of information, we may provide aggregate information to our partners about how our customers, collectively, use our Website or services. We share this type of statistical data so that our partners also understand how often people use the Website or services, so that they, too, may provide you with an optimal online experience. Again, never discloses aggregate information to a partner in a manner that would identify you personally.

**E-mail Communications:**

We often receive a confirmation when you open an email from if your computer supports this type of program. uses this confirmation to help us make emails more interesting and helpful. When you receive e-mail from , you can opt out of receiving further e-mails by following the included instructions to unsubscribe.

**What About Cookies?**

    * Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computers hard drive through your browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and tell us how and when pages in our site are visited and by how many people. We use cookies to enhance visitors experiences, to learn more about their use of the Website and to improve the quality of our services. 
    * Most browsers have an option for turning off the cookie feature, which will prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, as well as (depending on the sophistication of your browser software) allowing you to decide on acceptance of each new cookie in a variety of ways. We strongly recommend that you leave the cookies activated, however, because cookies enable you to take advantage of some of our Websites most attractive features.
    * Ads appearing on the Website may be delivered to users by our advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

Will Share Any of the Personal Information it Receives?

Personal Information about our customers is an integral part of our business. We neither rent nor sell your Personal Information to anyone. We share your Personal Information only as described below.

_Affiliated Businesses We Do Not Control_ : We anticipate that we may become affiliated with a variety of businesses and work closely with them. In certain situations, these businesses may sell items to you through the Website. In other situations, may provide services jointly with affiliated businesses. You can easily recognize when an affiliated business is associated with your transaction, and we will share your Personal Information that is related to such transactions with that affiliated business.

_Agents_ : We employ other companies and people to perform tasks on our behalf and need to share your information with them to provide products or services to you. Unless we tell you differently, Createandspread.com agents do not have any right to use Personal Information we share with them beyond what is necessary to assist us. You hereby consent to our sharing of Personal Information for the above purposes.

_Promotional Offers_ : We may send offers to you on behalf of other businesses. However, when we do so, we do not give the other business your name and address. If you do not wish to receive these offers, please send an email with your request to info@createandspread.com. 

_Business Transfers_ : In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, customer information is typically one of the business assets that are transferred. Moreover, if Createandspread.com, or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, customer information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of may continue to use your Personal Information as set forth in this policy.

_Protection of and Others_ : We may release Personal Information when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with the law; enforce or apply our conditions of use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of , our employees, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

_With Your Consent_ : Except as set forth above, you will be notified when your Personal Information may be shared with third parties, and will be able to prevent the sharing of this information.

CONDITIONS OF USE   

If you decide to visit the websites, your visit and any possible dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of California state law.    

THIRD PARTY WEBSITES; APPLICATIONS   

Createandspread.com services may permit you to link to other websites on the Internet, and other websites may contain links to the Websites. These other websites are not under control, and such links do not constitute an endorsement by of those other websites or the services offered through them. The privacy and security practices of websites linked to or from the websites are not covered by this Privacy Policy, and is not responsible for the privacy or security practices or the content of such websites.    

**SPECIFICALLY, the Website will link to Facebook webpages and provide links to various Facebook applications. HAS NO CONTROL OVER FACEBOOKS PRIVACY PRACTICES** **OR THE PRIVACY PRACTICES OF THE OWNERS OR OPERATORS OF ANY OF THE APPLICATIONS.**   

Is Personal Information About me Secure?

Your account Personal Information is protected by a password for your privacy and security. You need to ensure that there is no unauthorized access to your account and Personal Information by selecting and protecting your password appropriately and limiting access to your computer and browser by signing off after you have finished accessing your account.

Createandspread.com endeavors to protect user information to ensure that user account information is kept private, however, cannot guarantee the security of user account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors, may compromise the security of user information at any time. 

what personal information can i access?

Createandspread.com allows you to access certain personal information about you for the purpose of viewing, and in certain situations, updating that information. Please see your account settings for more information.    

What Choices Do I Have?

You may request deletion of your account by sending an e-mail to info@createandspread.com. Please note that some information may remain in our records after deletion of your account. 

If you do not wish to receive email or other mail from us, please indicate this preference during the registration process. Please note that if you do not want to receive legal notices from us, such as this Privacy Policy, those legal notices will still govern your use of the Website, and you are responsible for reviewing such legal notices for changes.

Changes to this Privacy Policy

Createandspread.com may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes in the way we use Personal Information, we will notify you by posting an announcement on our Website or sending you an email. Users are bound by any changes to the Privacy Policy when he or she uses the Website after such changes have been first posted.

Questions or Concerns

If you have any questions or concerns regarding privacy on our Website, please send us a detailed message at info@createandspread.com. We will make every effort to resolve your concerns.

Effective Date: April 25, 2011

Email: info@createandspread.com
